twnpnews.com 2000-10-07

# Privacy Statement

##  Privacy Statement for TWNP 

**TWNP** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ TWNP ](http://www.twnpnews.com/)

####  Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used for other purposes. Your IP address is stored on the Web Servers log File, it is used to let TWNP know where our visitors are coming from. 

We use WebTrends Live to conduct anonymous web traffic analysis for our site. While WebTrends Live makes use of cookies, no personal information is ever collected or analyzed by this service. For more information on WebTrends Live, please visit their site at <http://www.webtrendslive.com/privacy_policy.htm>. 

####  Cookies 

Our Site uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests.  Cookies are used on TWNP to store Preferences in our Message Forum and Online Games. 

####  Advertisers 

We a few third party ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

TWNP works Flycast, a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Flycast manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html>. 

TWNP works with Advertising.com, a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Advertising.com manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.advertising.com/privacy/index.html>. 

TWNP works with FocusIN, a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how FocusIN manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.focusin.com/privacy.htm>. 

TWNP works with Clear Blue Media, a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Clear Blue Media manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.clearbluemedia.com/privacy.html>. 

TWNP works with Burst!, a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Burst! manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.burstmedia.com/release/privacy.asp>. 

TWNP works with ContentZone, a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Content Zone manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.247media.com/privacy.html>. 

####  Order Forms 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), unique identifiers (like their social security number), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). 

Contact information from the order forms is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. The customer's contact information is also used for other purposes. Your contact information is used in order forms to verify who you are. 

Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.  To help us serve our Advertisers better. 

####  Surveys 

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like email address), financial information (like account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). 

Contact information from the surveys is used for other purposes. To help us serve our Advertisers better. 

Financial information that is collected is used for other purposes. To order products at TWNP. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

####  Contests 

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like email address). 

Contact information from the contests is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. 

####  External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **TWNP** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

####  Public Forums 

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

####  Children's Guidelines 

We care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children: 

  1. We will NOT collect, use, or distribute to third parties personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent. 
  2. We will NOT give the child access to unmonitored chat rooms, message boards, email accounts, or other services that would give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent 
  3. When verifiable parental consent is not obtained, we will only use the online contact information (such as email) to: 
    1. Respond directly to the child's request on a one-time basis and not use that information to re-contact the child for other purposes. 
    2. Request the name or online contact information of a parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification. 
    3. Respond more than once directly to a specific request from a child (such as in the case where a child requests a newsletter subscription) and not used to re-contact the child for other purposes. We will use our best efforts to provide parental notification, which will include the nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information and participation in the activity. 
  4. We will NOT entice the child to divulge more information than is needed to participate in any activity, game, or service. 
  5. We will provide the parent a description of the specific types of a personally identifiable information collected from their child upon request. We will allow the parent to refuse further use or future online collection of personally identifiable information and provide a way for a parent to obtain any personally identifiable information collected from their child. 
  6. We will provide notice to children in age appropriate terms of what personally identifiable information is to be collected. 
  7. We will NOT provide any links to Web sites that are unsuitable for children. 
  8. We will encourage children to get their parent's permission before sharing personal information online. 

##  Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
